ANUJIT NENE

Pune, Maharashtra, India, 411038

Mobile: +91-9773999343

Email: anujitnene@qmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anujit-nene

Github: https://github.com/anujit

Profile

Javascript developer with 7.5 years of professional experience in developing web applications. Currently at Amdocs as an advanced software developer, I am working on building the frontend of enterprise grade applications for some of the biggest telecom providers using React, Redux, ES2015 and TypeScript. I believe in choosing the right tool for the job and am keen to explore and learn new technologies and frameworks as needed.

Technical Expertise

- Javascript, ES2015 (ES6), Typescript
- React, Redux, Webpack
- jQuery, AngularJS
- HTML, CSS
- Some experience working with NodeJS, ExpressJS
- NPM, Yarn
- Git, Perforce
- Working knowledge of TDD in ReactJS applications
- Familiarity with core Java, OCP, Spring, Microservices based architecture, AWS
- Working knowledge of using Jenkins CI/CD pipelines

Career History

Amdocs India Pvt Ltd, Pune, India

Jan 2018 - Present

Software Developer - Advanced

- I am a part of the product team as a UI developer building the Amdocs core Digital Experience enterprise product which is a complete e-commerce web application using React, Redux, ES2015, Typescript on the front-end
- Develop new, scalable UI features and enhancements in different modules as per the product releases for clients like Vodafone Italy, Sprint, 3IE
- Exposure to AEM (Adobe Experience Manager) content management platform as a part of the front end deliverables
- Experience working with CI/CD processes using Jenkins
- Working closely with Product Owners, Backend developers and other stakeholders in an Agile fashion

- Mentoring junior developers
- Working with a multi regional team located in Israel, France, US
- Worked on migration of a layer of our codebase to Typescript.
- Worked on building self-service journeys at https://vodafone.it

Globant, Pune, India

Feb 2016 – Jan 2018

Senior Software Engineer (Web UI Developer)

- Worked on AngularJS 1.x, React and NodeJS to develop different modules, features and SPAs for clients and projects across different business domains
- Some of the projects I worked on here include a self-service cloud services web app for Zerostack, a process management web-application for Autodesk among others
- Adhered to coding guidelines, style guides and overall best practices in UI development
- Worked in small dedicated teams for specific client or project

Sportz Interactive, Mumbai, India

Dec 2012 - Jan 2016

Associate - Development

- Sportz Interactive is an exciting company which provides technology and data solutions to companies in the sports business like Yahoo, Star, ISL, UEFA among others
- I developed different modules, Single Page Applications (SPAs) and other hosted solutions for sports data providers using HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery and other JS libraries as needed
- Part of the front-end team that built websites like indiansuperleague.com, sports.ndtv.com among others
- Adherence to delivery under tight deadlines for critical sports applications

Education

University of Mumbai, Mumbai, India **BE, Electronics Engineering**, Jun. 2012